The day of the shoot
Good morning!
I'm done with my makeup!
Look at my hair!
I have it here!
I ate it all!
Did you?
I'm still hungry.
Have you eaten?
No, I haven't.
I'm so happy to see you eat.
It's so good!
It's so sweet and delicious!
I like the potato pockle.
It was so good!
I was shocked when I first ate the
potato pockle.
I was like, wow, it's so good!
It's so good.
And the butter sandwich was so good.
It was so good.
I thought it would be more crispy, but
it was soft.
It's been a while since I ate this.
It was so good!
How was Hokkaido?
It was big!
It was good!
There were a lot of delicious food!
Aki-chan, you're already perfect with
your hair.
I'm done.
Today is the first day of the Z tour.
Did you sleep well last night?
I had a good night's sleep.
I couldn't sleep the day before
yesterday.
I slept at 5 o'clock.
It's the same!
It was long!
What time did you sleep?
I slept at 5 o'clock.
It's amazing.
It's 2.30 now.
It's late.
I usually sleep early.
I didn't sleep the day before
yesterday.
I was so excited.
I'm going to do a butt-hug.
This time, I was going to do a butt-hug
with a light.
But, I couldn't do it because of the
rain.
I watched the video three times.
It was fun.
You're already perfect.
Let's do our best!
This is a thumbnail.
It's a thumbnail.
Thumbnail is a gift.
Everyone gives me a gift.
I think so, too.
And, I saw a video of Royce's hair and
I recommended it.
So, I'm going to get it.
Sweet and sour one?
Yes, sweet and sour one.
I want to eat ramen, too.
Sapporo ramen?
Sapporo ramen.
Sweet and sour ramen.
We're going to prepare for the stage.
Next, we're going to change our
clothes.
Are we going to do it all?
One, two, three.
We're going to change our clothes.
This program is a program where six
people who are active to promote
something exciting challenge various
things to raise the excitement barometer
in the world.
I'll prove it to you.
Good morning!
Today,
we're going to have our first ZEPP tour
in Sapporo.
We're going to have a stylish tour.
We're wearing different clothes than
usual.
Yes, we are.
We're wearing a new hoodie.
I think it's cute.
This scarf is also cute.
There's a designer over there.
She hasn't put on makeup yet.
I'd like to ask her to introduce
herself.
She's a fashion designer.
Ms. Tsujino!
She's here!
I'm wearing a hoodie, too.
She's like a kid.
It's a hoodie made by CARATIN.
I'm wearing my own clothes today.
I've never worn this before.
I'm glad.
I wonder if anyone has it.
I think someone is wearing it today.
It's a little cool in Hokkaido today.
It's a little cooler than I expected.
I'm glad.
I'll do my best!
I just wanted to wear this and show it
to you.
I'm going to wear white clothes.
I'm going to wear a white face.
It's cute.
I'm glad.
I have something to say before I change
my clothes.
Can you hear me?
Actually, I put in my contacts today.
Finally, I can eat every day.
I'm so happy.
With such an effort.
Maria, you're always...
What's wrong with you?
I'm being shot.
Listen to me.
Today's 7 mysteries.
Not 7 mysteries, but one mystery.
As usual, I put in my contacts this
morning.
I put one spare contact in my carry
bag.
I brought six contacts.
I took out two contacts, one for each
eye.
I put one in the pan.
I put one in.
I was going to put in another one.
But the inside was empty.
What?
I thought it was strange.
I only have one in my bag.
I thought there was one empty.
I put two contacts in both eyes.
I took them out once.
But I couldn't see both eyes.
I only had one in my bag.
I thought it was one.
I looked again.
There was no water in it.
I brought one empty.
I only have one in my bag.
But I had spare contacts.
I was fine.
Your routine is to put in contacts from
your glasses.
I miss that.
You did that in English.
I did.
The 7 mysteries of spring.
We're in Hokkaido today.
Hokkaido is famous for delicious food
and souvenirs.
I brought a carry bag for a souvenir.
Me too.
You opened it.
It was empty.
It wasn't empty.
Really?
It wasn't full.
It's not a 7 mysteries.
I bought a lot of souvenirs for my mom.
I asked her to put in a souvenir if she
liked it.
I see.
It's half empty.
I have to put in a lot.
What are you going to buy?
First, I'm going to buy a Rolls Royce.
I'm going to buy a white neck and a
face.
It was delicious. Did you eat it?
I did.
It's delicious.
And pickles.
Pickles?
I'm going to buy pickles.
I'm going to buy something salty.
That's good.
I jumped with Aki-chan.
I jumped and I thought we would be
together next time.
But, I came here.
I remembered it.
I talked to her and came here.
I'm sorry.
Bye bye.
I can't focus well when I go this far.
I found it.
I'm going.
My white lover.
I'm a white lover.
Are you a lover?
You are a lover, aren't you?
You are a lover.
I'm a lover.
Please subscribe to my channel.
I'm going to sleep.
Good morning.
I got up.
Thank you for your viewing.
I'm wearing my school uniform today!
I'll do my best in Hokkaido!
See you later!
I'll go and change my clothes!
I'm done with my make-up!
We're done with stretching.
We're going to do a rehearsal.
I was watching you.
Oh, you were?
I have one thing to say.
I know you're not watching this.
Only KANOIN knows this fact.
I know.
Did our followers come here yesterday?
Yes we did.
Give you an introduction about our
members like
our favourite kind of sour- pulse fish
something like that.
If it was an octopus, it would be
small.
There were many kinds of squids and
octopuses.
We took many kinds of octopus.
And at the end, there was a huge squid
with a thick leg.
It was quite big.
Can I see it?
It was an octopus.
It was a big octopus.
It looked delicious.
It was big.
We couldn't cut it.
We didn't have a scissor or a knife.
So, we didn't eat it.
After that, we went to see it.
Then, Goharu, the shop assistant, asked
us if we could eat it.
I said yes.
I brought a pack of it.
Did you eat it?
The staff is laughing.
I want to eat it.
Thank you.
You wanted to eat it, didn't you?
And, Goharu, Inari, you ate three of
them.
No, no.
You ate two of them.
Did you eat it?
I ate it.
I'm happy to hear that.
As a result, Goharu's stomach was full.
It's OK.
I'm glad that I could meet you.
I heard that the dinner last night was
delicious.
It's already decided.
Maybe it's delicious.
According to the rumor.
I can feel Hokkaido.
It's important.
What?
Jingisukan?
No.
Jingisukan.
I can hear it.
I can only hear it.
It's not a sports day.
It's better than I thought.
It's good.
It's close.
It's very close.
Please subscribe to this channel.
See you soon!
I'm going to use it.
I was going to come out from here, but
I'm sure I'll use it.
Bye bye.
I'm sure you're going to be like that
now.
As expected, Rio is a winner.
This time, too.
It's rehearsal.
Let's go to rehearsal.
July's cider
The day I spent with you
It's not a waste
It hurts, it hurts
I'll do my best
July's cider
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6
We are Super-Secret-Senbun.
Thank you for your support.
Today is the first day of the tour.
Yes.
This is the first day of the tour in
Sapporo.
Yes.
We will perform twice from the first
day.
Thank you for your support.
The first day of the tour.
Cut.
Can you do it again?
Practice week
The members of BELLY through the
interpreter
She's nice to UME
Her face brightens by this
MBTI is?
Kami's MBTI isc%, which have a lot of
positive S,  yesterday
However, there is a
unknownSpecificDevil
Next, we're going to reveal Another new
Sin of Devil
Translated by Releska
Thank you for watching.
Thank you for coming to the rehearsal.
Thank you for coming to the show.
The rehearsal is over.
I got a ticket.
I'm going to the rehearsal.
Bye Bye.
Let's jump.
Jump?
How about this?
Jump with heart and do the same.
Let's go.
One, two.
The two disappeared and Julia came
back.
We became one.
Bye bye. Let's go to the next one.
Ready, go!
You changed your clothes.
I have something to say.
What is it?
I'm looking forward to the next one.
When I changed my clothes, you said you
wanted to transform.
You said you wanted to transform when
you were in the lesson.
I think I did.
It's strange.
But it's fun in Hokkaido.
It's fun.
Sorry, Aki-chan.
I talked about my contact by myself.
I came here again to jump with Julia
and Hitoka.
I'm going to be betrayed by Julia and
Hitoka.
I'm going to be betrayed.
Let's enjoy.
I want to dream.
I'll tell you that you are the best.
That's right.
Please wait for me.
I'm going to be betrayed.
Bye bye.
Thank you for watching.
Cute?
We are going to Hokkaido!
It's the first day of the Japan Tour!
We're starting from today!
We're in Hokkaido!
Where are we now?
We're in Zepp Sapporo!
I thought this was a backstage.
We're here!
I'm so happy!
This is Aki's first time on a trip.
How was it?
We came to Yuzubet before.
It was my first time in Hokkaido.
I was like,
I'm in Hokkaido!
I was so excited.
Let's enjoy the food!
I'm looking forward to tonight!
Let's do our best!
We'll be meeting you for the first time
in Hokkaido.
Let's do our best to make the best live
together!
We'll do our best!
Bye!
Ikuro!
Suji-danmae!
We've started.
Who are you?
I'm Ikigomi.
It's our first day.
We came here the day before yesterday.
It was a great time to travel abroad.
The plane was so exciting.
No matter how long we flew, it was so
fun.
What's wrong?
You're not like usual.
I'm fine.
Hiori is nervous.
I know.
No matter how long we fly.
What's wrong?
Please look forward to the next
episode!
This is our first live performance in
20 years!
I'm so happy that we can have our first
live performance on ZEPP TOUR.
We couldn't have our last ZEPP TOUR
last year, but we can finally have it
today.
I'm so happy that we can have this day
with our members, staff, and
advertisers.
We did a lot of rehearsals and
performed a lot of new songs.
It's our first time to show our new
outfits.
We can't come to Hokkaido often, so I
think there are many people who can't
meet us or see us for the first time.
We will do our best to make them
excited.
We will do our best!
We have a lot of new songs.
We are like, we have this song!
We will do our best!
We are going to start our first live
performance!
This is our first live performance on
ZEPP TOUR.
I'm getting excited.
It's been a long time since we last
came to Hokkaido.
We ate salmon roe in 2019.
It's a memory.
It's been a long time.
All members didn't eat salmon roe.
We ate it as a pre-meal preparation.
So, we are holding it in our hands.
We are back in Hokkaido.
Let's get excited with everyone who
came to Hokkaido and have a great start!
We will do our best!
They are here. Welcome.
We are going to start our first live
performance.
Everyone, hold the mic.
I'm looking forward to it.
Let's start from the beginning.
It's starting.
It's exciting.
I'm excited.
We will be back soon.
Everyone who came to Hokkaido.
The ZEPP tour will start now.
It's starting!
Let's make the best ZEPP tour!
Thank you!
Let's enjoy it!
See you later!
KONOMI!
CHURIA!
HITOKA!
HARUKA!
AKI!
HIYORI!
Super exciting promotion!
ZEPP Tour starts now!
Yeaaay
Thank you everyone for coming today.
I think this was a very supportive time
for me.
Yay!
Hey, Aki-chan, bring me a white lover!
I'll give it to you.
I'm sorry.
When I came back to this rehearsal,
everyone applauded and welcomed us.
When I heard the song of Tokisen,
the endless of the first rehearsal,
I was supported by myself.
Well.
Mingen.
This useful part, I will remove.
There are many people who shed tears
for us, and staff members who watch our
dreams.
And my family who always supports me.
I'm so happy that they say welcome
home.
I feel that it's not a common thing to
meet like this.
I had a lot of frustrations and hard
times.
But I'm getting stronger.
I want to be stronger for everyone.
I want everyone to think of us and
become stronger.
I want to be more confident and make my
dreams come true.
I can't give up so easily.
I'm supported by so many people.
I want to repay them little by little.
I had a lot of parts that didn't go as
I planned.
I want to do my best so that everyone
can be more confident.
I love everyone. Thank you.
I'm sorry.
We love you, Moa.
We love you.
Julia, say it again.
I'm happy.
The first performance of the first day
of the concert was over.
It's over.
Thank you for your hard work.
I got it.
I finished my part.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'll buy one more box.
I'm serious.
Buy it for me.
Let's buy the most large-capacity one
and share it.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'll buy it.
I'm hungry.
What do you want to eat?
Rib-eye steak.
I got this from the manager.
It's pudding.
It smells good. Mango pudding.
I love mango.
Let's eat.
Please subscribe to my channel.
I dyed my hair to a new color.
I'm still wearing my old hair.
Oh, she's here.
She's here! She's here!
Twin tails?
Pony tails?
I'm a boy!
It's been a while!
I haven't done this in a while.
It's been a while.
Hi, everyone!
It's been a while!
I'm looking forward to the event!
What's your souvenir, Kamika-san?
Did you decide?
I bought a white one.
I also bought a potato chip and a
butter sandwich.
And I also bought a potato chip with
chocolate on it.
That's really good!
I got that!
Did you get it?
There are a lot of delicious things.
What was it?
I forgot.
What was that?
Potato chip.
Delivery?
I forgot.
There's a snack with onion.
I talked about it earlier, but I
forgot.
I'll eat that, too.
Please enjoy the food in Hokkaido!
I'll tell you about it on Instagram.
I'll tell you about it tomorrow.
Let's go there today!
Let's go!
I'll ask Akita to teach me that!
I'll send it to everyone!
Please send it to me!
I'll tell you what I bought on my blog!
I'll send it to you!
Please watch it!
I'm looking forward to it!
Let's buy a lot of souvenirs and go
home!
Let's go home!
Hokkaido is great!
I'm wearing a twin tail!
Now, the second part of the tour in
Hokkaido, Zepp, Sapporo, will start!
Oh, no. If this is over, it's the end
of the 100th episode.
I don't want to think about it.
I don't want to.
Well, Kanamin.
Well, Aki-chan said it earlier.
It's a different camera.
Oh, really?
I'll say it again.
Say the real thing about Kanamin.
At the end of the first chorus, there's
a line,
I made a mistake in saying that.
I thought, Oh, no.
You're wearing a hat.
I was surprised that my voice was
different from my image.
I was laughing.
The staff is taking a video.
I saw it and I thought, I did it.
Actually,
You're in love, too.
I'm in love.
But you're always in love.
It's a lie.
I wanted to say it like a joke.
I really wanted to say it.
I thought, Oh, no.
Hey, hey, hey, it's the first time.
I'll do my best.
Me, too.
I'll take a day off on the second day.
What? On the second day?
No, no, no.
Then I'll ask Kanami.
I can't do that.
I'm a little nervous.
Hey, hey, you said you like me, didn't
you?
You said you like me, didn't you?
Thanks for watching!
Look at this.
It's Chibi.
Cute Chibi.
Big.
I found a salmon roe.
It's shining. It's like a real anthem.
Oh, you came.
How much do you want?
I don't need it.
Please take responsibility and love me.
I say a little selfish things.
Look at her. She is so cute today.
Shall we get ready?
Last in Hokkaido.
Let's go.
I'm going to the airport.
I love you.
Thank you. I'll do my best.
Tanomi! Julia! Hitoka! Haruko! Aki!
Kiyori! Super-exciting advertisement!
Rock'n'Roll!
It's awesome.
1 minute left
The Great Mountain Reappears
Thank you for watching!
Let's do our best!
OK let's try it again
Thank you for watching.
Is Choba Chua okay?
Yes, it is.
Thank you for watching! Please
subscribe to my channel!
Free Tokinaka
There might have been more pope than I
did, which is fun!
I am going to take a moment and say,
Perhaps a big thank you and a big thank
you to everyone.
Sanriki Comedy Hunt,
the U2 made their perfect comeback in
2012,
Thank you for watching.
Thank you for your hard work!
It was fun!
Good job!
I'm so happy!
I'm glad I didn't collapse at the end.
Thank you for your hard work.
Your cute face is the problem.
Eat delicious food and sleep a lot.
I feel treasured today.
So, our first day at Hadairo Sapporo
performance finally came to an end!
Thank you!
Good job, everyone!
We were able to finish our first day
successfully.
I'm glad.
We had two shows this time, and we were
really excited.
We started!
We were excited to see if it had
started.
It was a very fun and exciting live.
We all worked hard for two minutes, so
I think it was a good first day.
It was a good first day.
Next is Nagoya.
Shall we fly?
Let's fly!
Let's fly together.
Let's hold hands and fly together.
Let's go.
Ready?
I want to see you in the same way
I want to make you more and more
absorbed in tears
Wherever you are
I'll make you smile alone
Cute
Tell me your love
I love you no matter how many times
Every day, morning, noon, and evening
Look at me
Anytime, I need you
Don't talk to other girls
It's okay
You want to be a good 20-year-old,
right?
Yes
20-year-old
We are a 20-year-old duo
It's our first...
Introduction?
Since the day I met you
My every day has changed into a love
comedy
I like you, I like you, I like you, I
like you
The existence of you, everything for
you
It's about to burst, I can't hold it in
anymore
I hope we can be together someday
When I saw a dream, a light ran through
my heart.
Absolutely, absolutely, absolutely,
this is fate.
Hey, look, I'm so excited.
You're the only one in the world.
I want to scream.
We met a week ago.
You're Naito, right?
Who are you?
What are you doing here?
I'm making a game here.
A game?
This is an invitation from the creator.
Creator?
That?
The legendary game creator group.
Creator.
We challenged ourselves to many
mysteries to play the new game created
by the creator.
Let's make it a success.
The first time in a long time
What's wrong?
We don't have time.
Rock on!
Survive!
Can they clear the game?
I can't be late.
I'll make the time.
You can't do it.
What should I do?
I won't let you!
Tom & Soya in the city.
Our Tori Day
How many points?
52 points.
It's normal.
The end.
To be continued.
I was supposed to do a ZEPP tour last
year, but due to various circumstances,
this time it will be a ZEPP tour for a
year.
As a super-tourist, I will be doing a
trip to Hokkaido, Osaka, Nagoya, and
Fukuoka for the first time.
I'm full of motivation to rock on
everyone's hearts.
It was my dream to do a ZEPP tour.
Last year, it was postponed, but this
year it's a revenge, so I was really
looking forward to this tour.
I'm really looking forward to the
moment when my dream comes true.
There are people who are looking
forward to me, and there are people who
say,
I can do my best because I have Aki-
chan.
When there are such people, I will do
my best.
I think we are here because there is a
publicity manager.
Last year, when Aki-chan came in, I
couldn't do a live at all.
I thought it was hard to do it at a
time when I couldn't do it.
I think it was a difficult time to meet
and have fun.
I learned a lot from this activity that
if you do it all the time with the
spirit of having no choice but to do it,
you will be rewarded.
No matter how hard it is, there is a
light ahead.
I couldn't do a live at all.
I think there are days when I can't go
as I want after I become a super special
student.
I told myself that I did my best even
if I was the worst on that day.
I thought it would be nice if our
feelings were conveyed to the fans.
I thought that I could convey that a
good day would come.
Let's go!
Tumo Tumo Tumorou Saikyou Zetsu
Say hello to the new me
It doesn't matter what they say
Let's go all out!
Tumo Tumo Tumorou Saikyou Zetsu
Say hello to the infinite possibilities
Challenge everything you want to do
Prove the exciting future
Ah!
Happy New Day!
никто의 소년들이 영원히 돕는 댓글의 메세지에
Please subscribe to my channel!
I remember the reason I cried and the
time I was lost
Even if it rains, I'll go wherever I
can to smile
Goodbye, goodbye, I'm the same as
yesterday
The city lights after the rain are
sparkling
My heart is like a sunny day, the
rainbow is ringing
I'll play the rainbow piano
Goodbye, goodbye, I'm the same as
yesterday
The city lights after the rain are
sparkling
My heart is like a sunny day, the
rainbow is ringing
I'll play the rainbow piano